coastalfitnesshk.com 2011-09-06

# Privacy Policy : Coastal Fitness HK (Hong Kong)

### Our commitment to privacy

Coastal Fitness is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you accept the practices described here. Coastal Fitness may occasionally change this policy by updating this page. Please constantly refer back to this page to ensure that you are aware with any changes. This policy is effective from November 1st, 2009.

### How we use information

The information that you provide is used to confirm bookings and as a means of personal contact so that we can reach you directly. We do not share your personally identifiable information to any third party for marketing purposes. However, we may share information with governmental agencies when required by law.

### Our commitment to data security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

Our site may use cookies which are useful for gathering information such as tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website being viewed.

### How you can access or correct your information

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. If you would like a copy of the information held on you, send us an email at: info@coastalfitnesshk.com . If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, email us as soon as possible, at the above email address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

### Privacy contact information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments, feel free to send us an email at: info@coastalfitnesshk.com

## Terms of Use

### General disclaimer

The following describes the terms and conditions that govern your use of the website. Your purchase or use of our products or service implies that you have read and accepted to be bound by these Terms of Use. We reserve the right to modify, add, remove, amend or restate portions of these Terms of Use from time to time with or without prior notice. Itâ€™s your responsibility to check these Terms of Use periodically for changes. We are not responsible for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential or any other damages arising out of or in connection with the use of this web site. This includes any personal injury, business interruption, loss of use, lost data, lost profits, or any other pecuniary loss, whether in an action of contract, negligence, or other tortuous action, even if we have been informed of the possibility.

### Currency

All prices on this site are in Hong Kong Dollars (HKD).

### Payments

Payment to Coastal Fitness can be made through cash, cheque or bank transfer. Payment information will be found on your invoice or in your order.

### Miscellaneous

Trademarks, service marks, product names and company names or logos appearing on coastalfitnesshk.com that are not owned by coastalfitnesshk.com may not be used or distributed without express permission from their owners. There may be links to other websites from the coastalfitnesshk.com website; however, these other websites are not controlled by coastalfitnesshk.com and we are not responsible for any content contained on any such websites or any loss suffered by you in relation to your use of such websites. You waive any and all claims against coastalfitnesshk.com and its directors, employees, affiliates or other representatives regarding the inclusion of links to outside websites or your use of those websites. The content of this website, including but not limited to text, graphics, designs, photographs, are protected by copyrights and other intellectual property rights. Except as expressly provided in these Terms of Use, no part of the website may be copied, reproduced, republished, posted, publicly displayed, transmitted or distributed in any way, without coastalfitnesshk.comâ€™s express prior written consent. This Agreement shall be governed by the laws of Hong Kong SAR, CN.

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments, feel free to send us an email at: info@coastalfitnesshk.com
